<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Form xmlns="http://v8.1c.ru/8.3/xcf/logform" xmlns:app="http://v8.1c.ru/8.2/managed-application/core" xmlns:cfg="http://v8.1c.ru/8.1/data/enterprise/current-config" xmlns:dcscor="http://v8.1c.ru/8.1/data-composition-system/core" xmlns:dcsset="http://v8.1c.ru/8.1/data-composition-system/settings" xmlns:ent="http://v8.1c.ru/8.1/data/enterprise" xmlns:lf="http://v8.1c.ru/8.2/managed-application/logform" xmlns:style="http://v8.1c.ru/8.1/data/ui/style" xmlns:sys="http://v8.1c.ru/8.1/data/ui/fonts/system" xmlns:v8="http://v8.1c.ru/8.1/data/core" xmlns:v8ui="http://v8.1c.ru/8.1/data/ui" xmlns:web="http://v8.1c.ru/8.1/data/ui/colors/web" xmlns:win="http://v8.1c.ru/8.1/data/ui/colors/windows" xmlns:xr="http://v8.1c.ru/8.3/xcf/readable" xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="2.1">
	<Title>
		<v8:item>
			<v8:lang>ru</v8:lang>
			<v8:content>Письмо Автору программы</v8:content>
		</v8:item>
		<v8:item>
			<v8:lang>en</v8:lang>
			<v8:content>Letter to the author of the program</v8:content>
		</v8:item>
		<v8:item>
			<v8:lang>ro</v8:lang>
			<v8:content>Scrisoare de autor al programului</v8:content>
		</v8:item>
		<v8:item>
			<v8:lang>bl</v8:lang>
			<v8:content>Ліст Аўтару праграмы</v8:content>
		</v8:item>
		<v8:item>
			<v8:lang>zh</v8:lang>
			<v8:content>程序作者的信</v8:content>
		</v8:item>
		<v8:item>
			<v8:lang>uk</v8:lang>
			<v8:content>Лист Автору програми</v8:content>
		</v8:item>
		<v8:item>
			<v8:lang>BG</v8:lang>
			<v8:content>Писмо до автора на програмата</v8:content>
		</v8:item>
		<v8:item>
			<v8:lang>DE</v8:lang>
			<v8:content>Brief an den Autor des Programms</v8:content>
		</v8:item>
		<v8:item>
			<v8:lang>PL</v8:lang>
			<v8:content>List do autora programu</v8:content>
		</v8:item>
		<v8:item>
			<v8:lang>kk</v8:lang>
			<v8:content>Хат бағдарламаның авторына</v8:content>
		</v8:item>
		<v8:item>
			<v8:lang>th</v8:lang>
			<v8:content>จดหมายถึงผู้เขียนโปรแกรม</v8:content>
		</v8:item>
	</Title>
	<AutoSaveDataInSettings>Use</AutoSaveDataInSettings>
	<AutoTitle>false</AutoTitle>
	<ScalingMode>Compact</ScalingMode>
	<AutoCommandBar name="ФормаКоманднаяПанель" id="-1">
		<Autofill>false</Autofill>
	</AutoCommandBar>
	<Events>
		<Event name="OnOpen">ПриОткрытии</Event>
		<Event name="OnCreateAtServer">ПриСозданииНаСервере</Event>
		<Event name="OnClose">ПриЗакрытии</Event>
	</Events>
	<ChildItems>
		<LabelDecoration name="ПрограммаЭлементарнаяТорговля" id="10">
			<TextColor>#000064</TextColor>
			<Title formatted="false">
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>ru</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Программа Элементарная Торговля была написана в октябре 2013 года и постоянно развивается. 

Если Вы обнаружили ошибку в программе или желаете добавить определенный функционал, то можете открыть в интернете сайт программы. На этом сайте можно обнаружить документацию по программе, свежую версию программы, а также задать вопрос автору или другим пользователям.


Программа условно-бесплатная. Поэтому гарантирована поддержка только тем, кто ее приобрел.
Автор программы заинтересован в решении вопросов и поддержке остальных поьзователей, но не может гарантировать им своевременный и полный ответ.</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>en</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Elementary Program Trade was written in October 2013 and is constantly evolving.

If you find a bug in the program or would like to add a specific functionality, you can open the Internet site of the program. On this website you can find documentation on the program, the latest version of the program, as well asask the author or other users.


The program is shareware. Therefore, support is guaranteed only to those who have acquired.
Author of this program is interested in issues and support for the rest of the user is, but can not guarantee their timely and comprehensive response.</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>ro</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Elementare Trade Programul a fost scris în octombrie 2013 și este în continuă evoluție.

Dacă ați găsit un bug în program sau ar dori să adăugați o funcționalitate specifică, puteți deschide site-ul internet al programului. Pe acest site puteți găsi documentație privind programul, cea mai recentă versiune a programului, precum și cere ca autor sau a altor utilizatori.


Programul este shareware. Prin urmare, sprijinul este garantat doar pentru cei care au dobândit.
Autorul acestui program este interesat de problemele și de sprijin pentru restul de utilizator este, dar nu poate garanta răspunsul lor în timp util și cuprinzătoare.</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>bl</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Праграма Элементарная Гандаль была напісана ў кастрычніку 2013 года і ўвесь час развіваецца.

Калі Вы знайшлі памылку ў праграме або жадаеце дадаць пэўны функцыянал, то можаце адкрыць у інтэрнэце сайт праграмы. На гэтым сайце можна выявіць дакументацыю па праграме, свежую версію праграмы, а таксама задаць пытанне аўтару ці іншым карыстальнікам.</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>zh</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>写于2013年10月和小学课程贸易也在不断发展。

如果您发现程序中的错误，或者想添加特定的功能，你可以打开Internet站点的程序。在这个网站上，你可以找到文档程序，最新版本的程序，以及请作者或其他用户。


该计划是共享的。因此，支持保证只收购那些谁。
这个程序的作者是感兴趣的问题和其余用户的支持，但不能保证他们及时和全面的答复。</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>uk</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Програма Елементарна Торгівля була написана в жовтні 2013 року і постійно розвивається.

Якщо Ви виявили помилку в програмі або бажаєте додати певний функціонал, то можете відкрити в інтернеті сайт програми. На цьому сайті можна виявити документацію за програмою, свіжу версію програми, а також задати питання автору або іншим користувачам.


Програма умовно-безкоштовна. Тому гарантована підтримка тільки тим, хто її придбав.
Автор програми зацікавлений у вирішенні питань і підтримці інших поьзователя, але не може гарантувати їм своєчасний та повний відповідь.</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>BG</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Начално програма търговия е написана през октомври 2013 г. и се развива непрекъснато.

Ако намерите бъг в програмата или желаете да се добави конкретна функционалност, можете да отворите интернет страницата на програмата. На този сайт можете да намерите документацията на програмата, най-новата версия на програмата, както и да поиска от автора или други потребители.


Програмата е Shareware. Следователно, подкрепа е гарантирана само за тези, които не са получили.
Автор на тази програма се интересуват от въпроси, и подкрепа за останалата част на потребител е, но не може да гарантира тяхното навременно и изчерпателен отговор.</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>DE</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Elementary Programm Handel wurde im Oktober 2013 geschrieben und wird ständig weiterentwickelt.

Wenn Sie einen Fehler im Programm oder finden möchte, um eine bestimmte Funktionalität hinzufügen, können Sie öffnen Sie die Internet-Seite des Programms. Auf dieser Website finden Sie Dokumentation auf dem Programm, die neueste Version des Programms, sowie den Autor fragen oder anderen Nutzern.


Das Programm ist Shareware. Daher wird die Unterstützung nur für diejenigen, die erworben haben garantiert.
Autor dieses Programms interessiert sich für Fragen und Unterstützung für den Rest der Benutzer ist, kann aber nicht garantieren, ihre rechtzeitige und umfassende Antwort.</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>PL</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Elementary Trade Program powstał w październiku 2013 roku, stale się rozwija.

Jeśli znajdziesz błąd w programie lub chciałbyś dodać określoną funkcjonalność, można otworzyć stronę internetową programu. Na tej stronie można znaleźć dokumentację na temat programu, najnowsza wersja programu, a także zwrócić się do autora lub innych użytkowników.


Program jest shareware. Dlatego też wsparcie jest zapewnione tylko do tych, którzy nabyli.
Autor tego programu jest zainteresowany kwestii i wsparcie dla reszty użytkowników, ale nie może zagwarantować ich terminowe i wyczerpujące odpowiedzi.</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>kk</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Бағдарлама сауда элементарная 2013 жылдың қазанында жазып қой- болды және ылғи дамиды.   </v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>th</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>ประถมศึกษา โปรแกรม การค้า เป็นหนังสือที่เขียน ในเดือนตุลาคม ปี 2013 และ มีการพัฒนา อย่างต่อเนื่อง

หากคุณ พบข้อผิดพลาด ในโปรแกรมหรือต้องการที่จะ เพิ่ม การทำงานบางอย่าง ที่คุณสามารถเปิด เว็บไซต์ อินเทอร์เน็ต ของโปรแกรม ในเว็บไซต์นี้คุณ สามารถหาเอกสาร ในโปรแกรม รุ่น ล่าสุดของโปรแกรมรวมทั้ง ขอให้ ผู้เขียน หรือผู้ใช้ อื่น ๆ


โปรแกรม แชร์แวร์ ดังนั้น การสนับสนุน จะรับประกัน เฉพาะกับผู้ที่ ได้สั่งซื้อ
ผู้เขียนโปรแกรม นี้ มีความสนใจใน ปัญหา และการสนับสนุน จากส่วนที่เหลือ ของผู้ใช้แต่ ไม่สามารถรับประกัน การตอบสนอง และครอบคลุม ของพวกเขา</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
			</Title>
			<BackColor>#F0FFFF</BackColor>
			<Border width="1">
				<v8ui:style xsi:type="v8ui:ControlBorderType">Underline</v8ui:style>
			</Border>
			<ContextMenu name="ПрограммаЭлементарнаяТорговляКонтекстноеМеню" id="11"/>
			<ExtendedTooltip name="ПрограммаЭлементарнаяТорговляРасширеннаяПодсказка" id="12"/>
		</LabelDecoration>
		<LabelDecoration name="ОВозможности" id="31">
			<Title formatted="false">
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>ru</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Убедитесь, что 1С не закрыта брандмауэром Windows. Если письмо не удается отправить или, перейдите на сайт программы или отправьте его обычным способом по адресу sza@ukr.net</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>EN</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Ensure that 1C is not closed b</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>BG</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Уверете се, че защитната стена не е затворен 1C Windows. Ако не можете да изпратите имейл или да отидете на сайта на програмата или да го изпратите по обичайния начин при sza@ukr.net</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>BL</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Пераканайцеся, што 1С не зачыненая брандмаўарам Windows. Калі ліст не атрымоўваецца адправіць або, перайдзіце на сайт праграмы або адпраўце яго звычайным спосабам па адрасе sza@ukr.net</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>DE</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Stellen Sie sicher, dass die Firewall nicht geschlossen 1C von Windows. Wenn Sie eine E-Mail nicht senden oder besuchen Sie die Website des Programms oder senden Sie es in der üblichen Weise bei sza@ukr.net</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>PL</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Upewnij się, że zapora nie jest zamknięta 1C Windows. Jeśli nie możesz wysłać e-mail lub przejdź do strony programu lub wysłać go w zwykły sposób na sza@ukr.net</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>RO</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Asigurați-vă că firewall-ul nu este închis 1C Windows. Dacă nu puteți trimite un e-mail sau du-te la site-ul web al programului sau trimite-l în mod obișnuit la sza@ukr.net</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>UK</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Переконайтеся, що 1С не закриті брандмауером Windows. Якщо лист не вдається відправити або, перейдіть на сайт програми або надішліть його звичайним способом за адресою sza@ukr.net</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>TH</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>ตรวจสอบให้แน่ใจว่าไฟร์วอลล์ไม่ได้ปิด 1C วินโดวส์ ถ้าคุณไม่สามารถส่งอีเมลหรือไปที่เว็บไซต์ของโปรแกรมหรือส่งไปในทางปกติท​​ี่ sza@ukr.net</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>ZH</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>确保防火墙没有关闭1C的Windows。如果您无法发送电子邮件或访问程序的网站或通常的方式在sza@ukr.net发送</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
			</Title>
			<ContextMenu name="ОВозможностиКонтекстноеМеню" id="32"/>
			<ExtendedTooltip name="ОВозможностиРасширеннаяПодсказка" id="33"/>
		</LabelDecoration>
		<UsualGroup name="ГруппаОтКого" id="43">
			<Title>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>ru</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Группа от кого</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>BG</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Група от кого</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>BL</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Група ад каго</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>DE</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Gruppen, von denen</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>EN</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Group from whom</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>PL</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Grupa, od którego</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>RO</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Grup de la care</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>UK</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Група від кого</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>TH</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>กลุ่มจากผู้ที่</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>ZH</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>集团从谁</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
			</Title>
			<ToolTip>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>ru</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Группа от кого</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>BG</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Група от кого</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>BL</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Група ад каго</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>DE</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Gruppen, von denen</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>EN</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Group from whom</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>PL</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Grupa, od którego</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>RO</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Grup de la care</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>UK</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Група від кого</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>TH</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>กลุ่มจากผู้ที่</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>ZH</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>集团从谁</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
			</ToolTip>
			<Group>Horizontal</Group>
			<ShowTitle>false</ShowTitle>
			<ExtendedTooltip name="ГруппаОтКогоРасширеннаяПодсказка" id="44"/>
			<ChildItems>
				<InputField name="ОтКого" id="1">
					<DataPath>ОтКого</DataPath>
					<DefaultItem>true</DefaultItem>
					<HorizontalStretch>false</HorizontalStretch>
					<AutoMarkIncomplete>true</AutoMarkIncomplete>
					<TextColor>#800000</TextColor>
					<BorderColor>style:FieldBackColor</BorderColor>
					<Font ref="sys:DefaultGUIFont" height="12" kind="WindowsFont"/>
					<ContextMenu name="ОтКогоКонтекстноеМеню" id="2"/>
					<ExtendedTooltip name="ОтКогоРасширеннаяПодсказка" id="3"/>
				</InputField>
				<LabelDecoration name="НаЭтотАдресБудетОтправленОтветАвтора" id="40">
					<HorizontalStretch>true</HorizontalStretch>
					<TextColor>#643300</TextColor>
					<Title formatted="false">
						<v8:item>
							<v8:lang>ru</v8:lang>
							<v8:content>На этот адрес будет отправлен ответ автора!</v8:content>
						</v8:item>
						<v8:item>
							<v8:lang>BG</v8:lang>
							<v8:content>Този адрес ще бъде изпратен на отговор на автора!</v8:content>
						</v8:item>
						<v8:item>
							<v8:lang>BL</v8:lang>
							<v8:content>На гэты адрас будзе адпраўлены адказ аўтара!</v8:content>
						</v8:item>
						<v8:item>
							<v8:lang>DE</v8:lang>
							<v8:content>Diese Adresse wird auf die Antwort des Autors verschickt werden!</v8:content>
						</v8:item>
						<v8:item>
							<v8:lang>EN</v8:lang>
							<v8:content>This address will be sent to the author's response!</v8:content>
						</v8:item>
						<v8:item>
							<v8:lang>PL</v8:lang>
							<v8:content>Ten adres zostanie wysłany do odpowiedzi autora!</v8:content>
						</v8:item>
						<v8:item>
							<v8:lang>RO</v8:lang>
							<v8:content>Această adresă va fi trimis răspunsul autorului!</v8:content>
						</v8:item>
						<v8:item>
							<v8:lang>UK</v8:lang>
							<v8:content>На цю адресу буде відправлений відповідь автора!</v8:content>
						</v8:item>
						<v8:item>
							<v8:lang>TH</v8:lang>
							<v8:content>ที่อยู่นี้จะถูกส่งไปยังการตอบสนองของผู้เขียน!</v8:content>
						</v8:item>
						<v8:item>
							<v8:lang>ZH</v8:lang>
							<v8:content>这个地址将被发送到作者的回应！</v8:content>
						</v8:item>
					</Title>
					<ContextMenu name="НаЭтотАдресБудетОтправленОтветАвтораКонтекстноеМеню" id="41"/>
					<ExtendedTooltip name="НаЭтотАдресБудетОтправленОтветАвтораРасширеннаяПодсказка" id="42"/>
				</LabelDecoration>
			</ChildItems>
		</UsualGroup>
		<LabelDecoration name="ЕслиВыУкажитеВашЕмейл" id="34">
			<Title formatted="false">
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>ru</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Если вы укажите ваш емейл, то реакция автора должна поступить в течении суток. Если реакции не последовало, значит автор Вашего письма не получил. Отправьте копию обычным способом.</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>EN</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>If you enter your email, the response must be received in the website during the day. If no response, then the author has not received your letter. Send a copy in the usual way.</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>UK</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Якщо ви вкажіть ваш емейл, то реакція автора повинна надійти протягом доби. Якщо реакції не послідувало, значить автор Вашого листа не отримав. Надішліть копію звичайним способом.</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>ZH</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>如果您输入您的电子邮件，响应必须在网站白天接收。如果没有反应，那么笔者还没有收到你的信。发送一份拷贝以通常的方式。</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>RO</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Dacă introduceți adresa dvs. de email, răspunsul trebuie să fie primite pe site-ul în timpul zilei. În cazul în care nici un răspuns, atunci autorul nu a primit scrisoarea ta. Trimite o copie în mod obișnuit.</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>BL</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Калі вы пакажыце ваш емейл, то рэакцыя аўтара павінна паступіць на працягу сутак. Калі рэакцыі не было, значыць аўтар Вашага ліста не атрымаў. Адпраўце копію звычайным спосабам.</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>BG</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Ако въведете вашия имейл, отговорът трябва да бъде получено в сайта през деня. Ако няма отговор, след това авторът не е получил писмото. Изпрати копие по обичайния начин.</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>DE</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Wenn Sie Ihre E-Mail eingeben, muss die Antwort in der Website während des Tages aufgenommen werden kann. Wenn keine Antwort, dann hat der Autor nicht Ihren Brief erhalten. Senden Sie eine Kopie in der üblichen Weise.</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>PL</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Jeśli wpiszesz swój adres e-mail, odpowiedź musi być umieszczony w witrynie w ciągu dnia. Jeśli nie ma odpowiedzi, to autor nie otrzymał listu. Wyślij kopię w zwykły sposób.</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>TH</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>หากคุณป้อนอีเมลของคุณตอบสนองจะต้องได้รับในเว็บไซต์ในช่วงวันที่ หากไม่มีการตอบสนองจากนั้นผู้เขียนยังไม่ได้รับจดหมายของคุณ ส่งสำเนาในทางปกติ</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>kk</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Сендер сендердің емейл сілтеп жіберсем, то автордың реакция тәуліктің ағысында түсу должна. Реакции последовало, сіздің хатыңыздың авторы значит алмаппын. Көшірмені әдеттегі қиюмен жібер-.</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
			</Title>
			<ContextMenu name="ЕслиВыУкажитеВашЕмейлКонтекстноеМеню" id="35"/>
			<ExtendedTooltip name="ЕслиВыУкажитеВашЕмейлРасширеннаяПодсказка" id="36"/>
		</LabelDecoration>
		<InputField name="РегистрационныйКод" id="22">
			<DataPath>РегистрационныйКод</DataPath>
			<HorizontalStretch>false</HorizontalStretch>
			<TextColor>#800000</TextColor>
			<BackColor>#FFFAF0</BackColor>
			<BorderColor>style:FieldBackColor</BorderColor>
			<ContextMenu name="РегистрационныйКодКонтекстноеМеню" id="23"/>
			<ExtendedTooltip name="РегистрационныйКодРасширеннаяПодсказка" id="24"/>
		</InputField>
		<InputField name="ТемаСообщения" id="4">
			<DataPath>ТемаСообщения</DataPath>
			<TextColor>#800000</TextColor>
			<BackColor>#FFFFF0</BackColor>
			<BorderColor>style:FieldBackColor</BorderColor>
			<Font ref="sys:DefaultGUIFont" height="12" kind="WindowsFont"/>
			<ContextMenu name="ТемаСообщенияКонтекстноеМеню" id="5"/>
			<ExtendedTooltip name="ТемаСообщенияРасширеннаяПодсказка" id="6"/>
		</InputField>
		<InputField name="ТекстСообщения" id="7">
			<DataPath>ТекстСообщения</DataPath>
			<MultiLine>true</MultiLine>
			<Font ref="sys:DefaultGUIFont" height="11" kind="WindowsFont"/>
			<ContextMenu name="ТекстСообщенияКонтекстноеМеню" id="8"/>
			<ExtendedTooltip name="ТекстСообщенияРасширеннаяПодсказка" id="9"/>
		</InputField>
		<UsualGroup name="ГруппаКП" id="20">
			<Title>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>ru</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Группа КП</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>en</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>CP Group</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>ro</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>CP Group</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>bl</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Група КП</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>zh</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>正大集团</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>uk</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Група КП</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>BG</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>CP Group</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>DE</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>CP Group</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>PL</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>CP Grupa</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>kk</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>КП тобы</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>th</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>กลุ่มซีพี</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
			</Title>
			<ToolTip>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>ru</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Группа КП</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>en</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>CP Group</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>ro</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>CP Group</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>bl</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Група КП</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>zh</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>正大集团</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>uk</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Група КП</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>BG</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>CP Group</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>DE</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>CP Group</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>PL</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>CP Grupa</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>kk</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>КП тобы</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>th</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>กลุ่มซีพี</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
			</ToolTip>
			<Group>Horizontal</Group>
			<Representation>None</Representation>
			<ShowTitle>false</ShowTitle>
			<ExtendedTooltip name="ГруппаКПРасширеннаяПодсказка" id="21"/>
			<ChildItems>
				<LabelDecoration name="ПерейтиКСайтуПрограммыВИнтернет" id="37">
					<Title formatted="false">
						<v8:item>
							<v8:lang>ru</v8:lang>
							<v8:content>Перейти к сайту программы в интернет: www.ELTR.od.ua</v8:content>
						</v8:item>
						<v8:item>
							<v8:lang>EN</v8:lang>
							<v8:content>Go to the website of the program in the Internet: www.ELTR.od.ua</v8:content>
						</v8:item>
						<v8:item>
							<v8:lang>UK</v8:lang>
							<v8:content>Перейти до сайту програми в інтернет: www.ELTR.od.ua</v8:content>
						</v8:item>
						<v8:item>
							<v8:lang>ZH</v8:lang>
							<v8:content>去在互联网程序的网站：www.ELTR.od.ua</v8:content>
						</v8:item>
						<v8:item>
							<v8:lang>RO</v8:lang>
							<v8:content>Du-te la site-ul web al programului în Internet: www.ELTR.od.ua</v8:content>
						</v8:item>
						<v8:item>
							<v8:lang>BL</v8:lang>
							<v8:content>Перайсці да сайту праграмы ў інтэрнэт: www.ELTR.od.ua</v8:content>
						</v8:item>
						<v8:item>
							<v8:lang>BG</v8:lang>
							<v8:content>Отиди в сайта на програмата в интернет: www.ELTR.od.ua</v8:content>
						</v8:item>
						<v8:item>
							<v8:lang>DE</v8:lang>
							<v8:content>Auf der Website des Programms im Internet gehen: www.ELTR.od.ua</v8:content>
						</v8:item>
						<v8:item>
							<v8:lang>PL</v8:lang>
							<v8:content>Przejdź do strony programu w Internecie: www.ELTR.od.ua</v8:content>
						</v8:item>
						<v8:item>
							<v8:lang>TH</v8:lang>
							<v8:content>ไปที่เว็บไซต์ของโปรแกรมใน Internet: www.ELTR.od.ua</v8:content>
						</v8:item>
						<v8:item>
							<v8:lang>kk</v8:lang>
							<v8:content>Бағдарламаның сайту деген ауыс- интернет: </v8:content>
						</v8:item>
					</Title>
					<Hyperlink>true</Hyperlink>
					<ContextMenu name="ПерейтиКСайтуПрограммыВИнтернетКонтекстноеМеню" id="38"/>
					<ExtendedTooltip name="ПерейтиКСайтуПрограммыВИнтернетРасширеннаяПодсказка" id="39"/>
					<Events>
						<Event name="Click">ПерейтиКСайтуПрограммыВИнтернетНажатие</Event>
						<Event name="URLProcessing">ПерейтиКСайтуПрограммыВИнтернетОбработкаНавигационнойСсылки</Event>
					</Events>
				</LabelDecoration>
				<LabelDecoration name="Декорация1" id="25">
					<HorizontalStretch>true</HorizontalStretch>
					<ContextMenu name="Декорация1КонтекстноеМеню" id="26"/>
					<ExtendedTooltip name="Декорация1РасширеннаяПодсказка" id="27"/>
				</LabelDecoration>
				<Button name="ОтправитьПисьмо" id="16">
					<Type>UsualButton</Type>
					<DefaultButton>true</DefaultButton>
					<CommandName>Form.Command.ОтправитьПисьмо</CommandName>
					<Font ref="sys:DefaultGUIFont" height="10" kind="WindowsFont"/>
					<ExtendedTooltip name="ОтправитьПисьмоРасширеннаяПодсказка" id="17"/>
				</Button>
				<LabelDecoration name="Декорация2" id="28">
					<HorizontalStretch>false</HorizontalStretch>
					<ContextMenu name="Декорация2КонтекстноеМеню" id="29"/>
					<ExtendedTooltip name="Декорация2РасширеннаяПодсказка" id="30"/>
				</LabelDecoration>
				<Button name="Закрыть" id="18">
					<Type>UsualButton</Type>
					<Representation>PictureAndText</Representation>
					<OnlyInAllActions>true</OnlyInAllActions>
					<Width>15</Width>
					<CommandName>Form.StandardCommand.Close</CommandName>
					<Title>
						<v8:item>
							<v8:lang>ru</v8:lang>
							<v8:content>Закрыть</v8:content>
						</v8:item>
						<v8:item>
							<v8:lang>BG</v8:lang>
							<v8:content>Близо</v8:content>
						</v8:item>
						<v8:item>
							<v8:lang>BL</v8:lang>
							<v8:content>Зачыніць</v8:content>
						</v8:item>
						<v8:item>
							<v8:lang>DE</v8:lang>
							<v8:content>Schließen</v8:content>
						</v8:item>
						<v8:item>
							<v8:lang>EN</v8:lang>
							<v8:content>Close</v8:content>
						</v8:item>
						<v8:item>
							<v8:lang>PL</v8:lang>
							<v8:content>Blisko</v8:content>
						</v8:item>
						<v8:item>
							<v8:lang>RO</v8:lang>
							<v8:content>Închide</v8:content>
						</v8:item>
						<v8:item>
							<v8:lang>UK</v8:lang>
							<v8:content>Закрити</v8:content>
						</v8:item>
						<v8:item>
							<v8:lang>TH</v8:lang>
							<v8:content>ใกล้</v8:content>
						</v8:item>
						<v8:item>
							<v8:lang>ZH</v8:lang>
							<v8:content>关闭</v8:content>
						</v8:item>
						<v8:item>
							<v8:lang>kk</v8:lang>
							<v8:content>Жап-</v8:content>
						</v8:item>
					</Title>
					<ExtendedTooltip name="ЗакрытьРасширеннаяПодсказка" id="19"/>
				</Button>
			</ChildItems>
		</UsualGroup>
	</ChildItems>
	<Attributes>
		<Attribute name="ОтКого" id="1">
			<Title>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>en</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>From (email)</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>bl</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Ад каго (email)</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>bg</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>От (email)</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>zh</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>从 (email)</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>de</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Von (email)</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>pl</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Z (email)</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>ro</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Din (email)</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>ru</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>От кого (email)</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>uk</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Від кого (email)</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>kk</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Кімнен (email)</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>th</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>จาก (อีเมล)</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
			</Title>
			<Type>
				<v8:Type>xs:string</v8:Type>
				<v8:StringQualifiers>
					<v8:Length>0</v8:Length>
					<v8:AllowedLength>Variable</v8:AllowedLength>
				</v8:StringQualifiers>
			</Type>
			<Save>
				<Field>ОтКого</Field>
			</Save>
		</Attribute>
		<Attribute name="ТемаСообщения" id="2">
			<Title>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>ru</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Тема сообщения</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>en</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Subject</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>ro</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Subiect</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>bl</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Тэма паведамлення</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>zh</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>主题</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>uk</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Тема повідомлення</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>BG</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Предмет</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>DE</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Unterworfen</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>PL</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Przedmiot</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>kk</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Хабарламаның тақырыбы</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>th</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>เรื่อง</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
			</Title>
			<Type>
				<v8:Type>xs:string</v8:Type>
				<v8:StringQualifiers>
					<v8:Length>0</v8:Length>
					<v8:AllowedLength>Variable</v8:AllowedLength>
				</v8:StringQualifiers>
			</Type>
			<Save>
				<Field>ТемаСообщения</Field>
			</Save>
		</Attribute>
		<Attribute name="ТекстСообщения" id="3">
			<Title>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>ru</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Текст сообщения</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>en</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Text messages</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>ro</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Mesaje text</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>bl</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Тэкст паведамлення</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>zh</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>文本消息</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>uk</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Текст повідомлення</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>BG</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Текстови съобщения</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>DE</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Kurzmitteilungen</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>PL</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Wiadomości tekstowe</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>kk</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Хабарламаның мәтіні</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>th</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>ข่าวสาร</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
			</Title>
			<Type>
				<v8:Type>xs:string</v8:Type>
				<v8:StringQualifiers>
					<v8:Length>0</v8:Length>
					<v8:AllowedLength>Variable</v8:AllowedLength>
				</v8:StringQualifiers>
			</Type>
			<Save>
				<Field>ТекстСообщения</Field>
			</Save>
		</Attribute>
		<Attribute name="РегистрационныйКод" id="4">
			<Title>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>ru</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Регистрационный код (если есть)</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>en</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Registration code (if any)</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>ro</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Cod de înregistrare (dacă este cazul)</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>bl</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Рэгістрацыйны код (калі ёсць)</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>zh</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>注册代码（如果有的话）</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>uk</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Реєстраційний код (якщо є)</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>BG</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Регистрационен код (ако има такива)</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>DE</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Registrierungs-Code (falls vorhanden)</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>PL</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Kod rejestracyjny (jeśli istnieje)</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>kk</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Тірке- код (болсам)</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>th</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>รหัสลงทะเบียน (ถ้ามี)</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
			</Title>
			<Type>
				<v8:Type>xs:string</v8:Type>
				<v8:StringQualifiers>
					<v8:Length>0</v8:Length>
					<v8:AllowedLength>Variable</v8:AllowedLength>
				</v8:StringQualifiers>
			</Type>
		</Attribute>
	</Attributes>
	<Commands>
		<Command name="ОтправитьПисьмо" id="1">
			<Title>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>ru</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Отправить письмо</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>en</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Send an email to</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>ro</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Trimite un e-mail la</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>bl</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Адправіць ліст</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>zh</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>发送电​​子邮件至</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>uk</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Відправити лист</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>BG</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Изпрати писмо на</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>DE</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Senden Sie eine E-Mail an</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>PL</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Wyślij e-mail do</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>kk</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Жібер- хат</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>th</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>ส่งจดหมาย</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
			</Title>
			<ToolTip>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>ru</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Отправить письмо</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>en</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Send an email to</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>ro</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Trimite un e-mail la</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>bl</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Адправіць ліст</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>zh</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>发送电​​子邮件至</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>uk</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Відправити лист</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>BG</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Изпрати писмо на</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>DE</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Senden Sie eine E-Mail an</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>PL</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Wyślij e-mail do</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>kk</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>Жібер- хат</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
				<v8:item>
					<v8:lang>th</v8:lang>
					<v8:content>ส่งจดหมาย</v8:content>
				</v8:item>
			</ToolTip>
			<Picture>
				<xr:Ref>CommonPicture.НовоеПисьмо</xr:Ref>
				<xr:LoadTransparent>true</xr:LoadTransparent>
			</Picture>
			<Action>ОтправитьПисьмо</Action>
			<Representation>TextPicture</Representation>
		</Command>
	</Commands>
</Form>